tradehub.net 2018-04-06

# Privacy Policy | ayondo.com

## Overview

Your privacy is important to us as it is our policy to reflect the confidentiality of information and the privacy of individuals.

We are bound by the Data Protection Act 1998.

This privacy policy covers:

  * Information we collect
  * Use of your information
  * Management and storage of the information
  * Your rights in respect of the information

## Information we collect

In order to meet our customers' needs effectively we need to collect certain personal information. We will collect the following: name, address, date of birth, contact details, income, assets, liabilities, account balances, employment details, tax and financial statements, trading statements and any other relevant information.

Most of the information comes directly from our customers through application forms and other requests for information, although we may from time to time obtain information from third party sources.

We may request other information to be supplied voluntarily in order to expand or develop our services to meet the need of existing and potential customers.

Should you choose not to provide information which we request, we may not be able to provide the service or product you require.

## Use of Information

We use the information primarily to establish and manage your account, review your needs and provide you with information regarding opportunities which we believe may be of interest to you.

We also use it to identify you when you contact us.

We may send you marketing information from time to time by email, telephone or other electronic messaging media unless you contact us to notify us that you do not wish to receive this information.

We disclose your information to our group companies and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf, for debit card validation and to credit agencies and fraud prevention agencies.

We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons.

Where required by law, your personal information may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental agency, regulatory body or enforcement authority.

These agencies may then use your personal information in respect of any alleged breach of law or regulatory rules.

## Management and Storage of Information

Our employees are trained to respect the confidentiality of customer information and we are committed to maintaining the security of the data we collect. We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse, incorrect exposure or alteration of the information.

## Your rights in respect of this Information

Under the Data Protection Act you have the right to obtain a copy of any personal information (for which we may charge a small fee) which we hold and correct any inaccuracies. We require a written request from you to supply this information.

You may request (in writing) not to receive any marketing material.

If our privacy policy changes our website will show the amended terms. We advise you to check for updates.

If you have any queries about this privacy policy contact our Customer Services department.
